bigbite.in 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy | Order food online from restaurants in Gurgaon, Noida and Delhi | bigbite.in

**Big Town Ideas Pvt. Ltd. (www.bigbite.in)** , are concerned about privacy issues and want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below). This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through the site from which you are accessing this policy (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy does not address the collection, use or disclosure of information by any of our affiliates or by third parties. By using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without prior notice. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the "LAST UPDATED" legend at the top of this page. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will become effective upon our posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Use of the Site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy then in effect. 

1\. What Types of Information Do We Collect From You?

**Personally Identifiable Information** (or " **PII** ") is information that identifies you as an individual. In order for you to take advantage of particular opportunities provided through the Site (for example, to use for the services offered on the Site), we may require that you furnish PII. We collect PII from you, such as your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number or other payment account number (including the three (3) or four (4) digit validation code for your credit card), when you voluntarily provide it to us or when your employer provides any such PII to us.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** (or " **Non-PII** ") is aggregated information, demographic information and any other information that does not reveal your specific identity. We and our third party service providers may collect Non-PII from you, including your MAC address, your computer type, screen resolution, OS version, Internet browser and demographic data, for example your location, gender and date of birth and we may aggregate PII in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of the Site, for example, by using PII to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code. Additionally, we and our third party service providers may collect Non-PII such as your employer's department code and expense code when provided to us by your or your employer. We and our third party service providers may also use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and other similar technologies to better serve you with more tailored information and facilitate your ongoing use of our Site. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to decline the use of cookies. To learn more about cookies, please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.

**IP Addresses** are the Internet Protocol addresses of the computers that you are using. Your IP Address is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). This number is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever users visit the Site, along with the time(s) of such visit(s) and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice on the Internet and is done automatically by many web sites.

2\. How Do We Use Information Collected From You?

**Personally Identifiable Information.** We may use PII:

 To fulfill your requests, e.g., to allow you to order food through our restaurant partners and have it delivered to you or to provide you with information that you request.

 To send you important information regarding the Site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information. Because this information may be important, you may not opt-out of receiving such communications.

 To inform you of products, programs, services and promotions that we believe may be of interest to you.

 To fulfill your purchase(s) (e.g., to process credit card payments in connection with your food order).

 To permit you to send messages regarding Site-related content to a friend through the Site. If you wish to use this feature, you may be required to provide us, and we may use, with your friend's email address to facilitate your sending of such message to your friend. By using this functionality, you affirm that you are entitled to use and provide us with the recipient's name and email address for this purpose. We will not to use your friend's PII for any other purpose other than to allow the message to be sent and/or to troubleshoot any issues with respect to the sending of such message, unless we disclose such other purpose to you at the time you provide such PII to us.

 To permit you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions (collectively, "Promotions"). You should carefully review the rules, if any, of each Promotion in which you participate, as they may contain additional important information about our use of your PII. To the extent that the terms and conditions of such rules concerning the treatment of your PII conflict with this Privacy Policy, the terms and conditions of such rules shall control.

 To customize content on our Site (e.g., the restaurants that will deliver to your location).

 For our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our website, improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns.

4\. Other Important Notices Regarding Our Privacy Practices.

Forums and Profiles. We may make available through the Site services (for example, message boards, chat functionality, "profile pages" and blogs, among other services) to which you are able to post information and materials. Please note that any information you disclose through such services becomes public information, and may be available to visitors to the Site and to the general public. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your PII, or any other information, on the Site. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE OF ANY PII YOU VOLUNTARILY DISCLOSE THROUGH THE SITE.

Third Party Sites. This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including without limitation any of our affiliates and any third party operating any site to which this Site contains a link. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us or by our affiliates.

Security. We use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect PII under our control. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please do not send us sensitive information through email. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the "Contacting Us" section below (note that if you choose to notify us via physical mail, this will delay the time it takes for us to respond to the problem).

Opt-Out. If you change your mind, and no longer wish to receive marketing-related e-mails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving such marketing-related e-mails or from such sharing by adjusting your preferences in the "My Account" section of the Site.

Changing or Suppressing PII. If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress or otherwise limit our use of your PII that has been previously provided to us, you may do so by adjusting your preferences in the "My Account" section of the Site. We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes, and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. Finally, we are not responsible for removing or suppressing information from the databases of third parties with whom we have already shared your PII, or limiting their use of your PII.

Retention Period. We will retain your PII for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

Note Regarding the Use of the Site by Children. The Site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that such individuals not provide PII through the Site.

Jurisdictional Issues. We do not represent or warrant that the Site, or any part thereof, is appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Site do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit the Site's availability, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion. 

Contacting Us. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at [policy@bigbite.in](mailto:policy@bigbite.in), or please write to the following address:  
Big Town Ideas Pvt Ltd,  
Attention: Bigbite Privacy Team  
F-413, Aditya Towers, Laxmi Nagar Dist. Centre,  
Laxmi Nagar- 110092
